Guide to the Ken Kennedy academic records, 1967-2007 MS 206
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VI: Academic papers, presentations, books and slides, 1971-2006 (Boxes 52-60)
  - Chapter 24 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Chapter 25 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - CRPC Book Draft (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - CRPC Book Ch 4 Draft/Revisions (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - CRPC Book Ch 20 Draft/Revisions (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - CRPC Book Ch 21 Draft/Revisions (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - CRPC Book Ch 22 Draft/Revisions (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - CRPC Book Ch 23 Draft/Revisions (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - CRPC Book Ch 24 Draft/Revisions (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - CRPC Book Ch 25 Draft/Revisions (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - CRPC Book Ch 11 and 12 Draft. 17 July 2002 (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - CRPC Book Illustration Drafts. 17 July 2002 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - CRPC Book Bibliography Draft/Revisions (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - CRPC Book Ch 3, 9, 12 and 17 and Correspondence (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Fax from Linda Torczon. 12 Aug 2002 (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - CRPC Book Copy Edit Production Schedule (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - CRPC Book Information Needed from Authors (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - CRPC Book Production Schedules (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - CRPC Book as of 18 Dec 2001 (2f) (Box 59, Folder 43-44)
  - CRPC Book - final questions (Box 59, Folder 45)
  - CRPC Book - About the Authors (Box 59, Folder 46)
  - CRPC Book - final questions (Box 59, Folder 47)
  - CRPC Book - Bibliography (Box 59, Folder 48)
  - CRPC Book - Color Plates (Box 59, Folder 49)
  - Our Proposal 19 July 1983 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Motion to Dismiss Response (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Eunice Source License (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - RUnice Distribution Announcement (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - SRI Wollongong Papers Sent to Baker Botts (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Untulis Letter (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Original Eunice License (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Eunice Project Berkeley Joint Work (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Wollongong Eunice Letter (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Eunice (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Eunice Documentation Packet (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Eunice Documentation (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - McDowell Award 1995 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - IEEE Application - McDowell (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - IEEE - Willy Zwaenepoel (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Snir, Marc (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Who's Who #1 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Who's Who #2 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Honors (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Conflicts of Interest (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Ken Kennedy's Proposals Submitted in CY 2006 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - IBM Cell NDA 2006 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - IBM Fellowship Program (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - SRI International and the Wollongong Group v. Ken Kennedy and Rice University. May 1983 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Microsoft Meeting (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - SUN NDA 2005 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Documents to edit (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - McDowell Award (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - 1997 W. Wallace McDowell Award (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - "Unifying Vectorization, Parallelization, and Optimization: The Ardent Compiler" by Randy Allen (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Index for Kennedy/Allen Book. 9 Aug 2001 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Optimizing Compilers for Modern Architectures by Randy Allen and Ken Kennedy Chapter Drafts (3f) (Box 60, Folder 32-34)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences. 7 Nov 2005 (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Letter from Bill Joy re: Sun Microsystems. 10 March 2000 (Box 60, Folder 36)
- Series VII: Personal and awards, 1970-2007 (Boxes 60-65)
  - Subseries A: Personal
    - Ken's updates and contacts (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - Ken's to-do (Box 60, Folder 38)
    - Ken Kennedy's technical biography, June 1998; Five year plan, 1996-2001 (Box 60, Folder 39)
    - Brookhart, Walter - Patent Attorney 2004 (Box 60, Folder 40)
    - Biax Patent Case (Box 60, Folder 41)
    - Texas A (Box 60, Folder 42)
    - University of Washington 2003 (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - University of Illinois Computer Technology (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Lemelson - MIT Awards 2006 (Item not specified)
    - Rice University Service Award (Item not specified)
    - CIO Magazine Interview (phone call) (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - Endorsement of Keith and Linda's Book (Box 60, Folder 46)
    - CRAY Stock Info. 9 June 2006 (Box 60, Folder 47)
    - Phone call with Randy Bryant re: CCC Chair (Box 60, Folder 48)
    - Houston Partners. 7 Sept 2001 (Box 60, Folder 49)
    - MacWorld Conference and Expo. 7-11 Jan 2002 (Box 60, Folder 50)
    - MacWorld items/information (Box 60, Folder 51)
    - Teleconference with Princeton - Dean Search. 22 Feb 2002 (Box 60, Folder 52)
    - Teleconference with Princeton. 1 March 2002 (Box 60, Folder 53)
    - Ken's University Lecture 2003 (Box 60, Folder 54)
    - University Professor Lunch May 2003 (Box 60, Folder 55)
    - M.D. Anderson Authorization for Molecular Profiling Forms. Nov 2006 (Box 60, Folder 56)
    - Meeting with Lydia January 2007 (Box 60, Folder 57)
    - Rescheduling various meetings/calls January 2007 (Box 60, Folder 58)
    - Invitations to Events (Box 60, Folder 59)
    - McGraw-Hill Annual Editions Info (Box 60, Folder 60)
    - Texas A (Box 60, Folder 61)
    - Ken Kennedy Oral History Project with Thomas Haugh 2007 (Box 60, Folder 62)
    - Awards (Box 60, Folder 63)
    - HPC Innovation Awards (judging) (Box 60, Folder 64)
    - Distinguished Alumni Award/Honor (Box 60, Folder 67)
    - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 60, Folder 68)
    - Remembering Ken Kennedy 2007 (Box 60, Folder 69)
    - Misc. Rice News and Rice Threshers and other news clippings (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Misc. greeting cards, notes and letters (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Nomination for IEEE Award - July 2007 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Talk and Reception for Moshe and Ken. April 2002 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Parellel Profile (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Executive Recruiter for Dell asking for recommendations for candidates Oct 2003 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Appointment books - 1970, 1972-1974 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Appointment books - 1975 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Appointment books/record books - 1976, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Appointment book - 1982 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Appointment book - 1983 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Appointment book - 1984 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Appointment books - 1985 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Appointment book - 1986 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Appointment books - 1992 and 1993 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Appointment books - 1994-1995 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Appointment books - 1996 and 1997 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Appointment book - 1998 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Appointment books - 1999-2001 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Address Books, undated (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Phone Message Book 2001 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence/Christmas cards, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Letter from Morgan-Kaufman Publishers, Inc. 2 March 2000 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - SRI Int. and the Wollongong Group v. Rice University and Ken Kennedy. 1983 Documents (3f) (Box 62, Folder 2-4)
    - Letters of Recommendation/Reference written by Ken 1989-2000 (2f) (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
    - David B. Johnson Curriculum vitae and recommendations (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Application for Federal Employment 1991 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Princeton Materials (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Meeting with Mike Counterman re: Q Clearance Feb2004 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - ComputerWorld Honors Program Online Case Study (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - ComputerWorld Heroes Award Nomination (Ken) 2004 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Annual Survey on Rice Health Plans from CareData. 9 Aug 2001 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Students/Programs (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Wiley and Sons Inc. (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Nigerian Bank Scam (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Performance (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Sabbaticals (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Disclosure Statement (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Passports/IDs (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Awards (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Ken Kennedy Summary of Accomplishments Dec 31 2001 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - CS Dept. Web Site article (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - NY Times - 2 Aug 2001 Quote (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Rice News Article "Rice Names Two Faculty to Rank of University Professor) 10 April 2002 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Rice News Story Feb 2003 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - University Professor Lunch (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Job Offers (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Baker Institute (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Deanship (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Payroll Deductions 2002 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Moving Expenses (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - Almes, Guy (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - Berman, Fran (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - Chapman, Barbara (Box 62, Folder 35)
    - Poduska Family Correspondence 1998 (Box 62, Folder 36)
    - Saltz, Joel. IEEE Fellow Ref. Form (Box 62, Folder 37)
    - Schwartz, Jack 1999 (Box 62, Folder 38)
    - Smalley, Richard 1998-99 (Box 62, Folder 39)
    - Stratman, Leah (Box 62, Folder 40)
    - Tapia, Richard (Box 62, Folder 41)
    - Tapia (NAE Award) (Box 62, Folder 42)
    - Tapia - Habermann Award (Box 62, Folder 43)
    - Tapia - White Paper (Box 62, Folder 44)
    - Tapia (Hispanic Engineering Award) (Box 62, Folder 45)
    - Tapia - awards (Box 62, Folder 46)
    - Thomas, Gwen (Box 62, Folder 47)
    - Waterman, Todd Ryan (Box 62, Folder 48)
    - HPC Wire Interview (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - CIO Magazine 1 July 2001 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Ken's Five Year Plan and Tech Bio (Box 63, Folder -)
    - UPI "Digital test tube models cell structures" 21 Aug 2001 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - ComputerWorld 24 Sept 2001 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Texas Higher Education Academic Resource Guide 2002 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Internet.com 30 July 2002 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - New York Times Article about Fran Allen. 6 Aug 2002 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Bio IT World 8 Aug 2002 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - A Rice University Perspective on Software Engineering Licensing. November 2002 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Hewlett-Packard Video Testimony. 7 Nov 2002 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Conflict of interest (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Royalty Statements (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Gittings - Photo Information (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - NRC Faculty Survey 2007 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Kennedy service highlights 1998-1999 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Two page Kennedy information used for proposals 1995 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Kennedy Vitae and Bio, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Bio updates (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Curriculum Vitae updates (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Media Training (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Continental Video, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Pam Francis Photography re: CIO Magazine Photo Shoot 2001 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Kathy Buford (Ken's Bookkeeper) (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Patents (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - University Professor Lunches (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Nano. Bio. Info. Enviro. Brochure 2002 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Awards/Appointments (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Distinguished Alumni Award - Honors Dinner May 2002 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Distinguished Alumni Award (photo) 2002 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Kennedy party (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - Wai-Yee (Wendy) Wong Affidavit (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - ComputerWorld Honors Case Study Finalist (Box 63, Folder 32)
    - Letter of Commendation from President George W. Bush. 20 Dec 2001 (Box 63, Folder 33)
    - Letter of Commendation from President Bill Clinton. 19 August 1999 (Box 63, Folder 34)
    - Greeting Cards (Box 63, Folder 35)
    - Ken Kennedy Slides (Box 63, Folder 36)
    - Photos, undated (Box 63, Folder 37)
    - Award Certificates 1983-1995 (Box 63, Folder 38)
    - Eight 3-inch floppy diskettes ca. 1996 (Box 63, Folder 39)
    - 3 inch floppy diskettes 1990-98 (4f) (Box 63, Folder 40-43)
  - Subseries B: Awards
    - TERA - First compiled program, 1990 (Box 64)
    - The Academy of Medicine Engineering and Science pin / unknown pin (Box 64)
    - Medallion - Computerworld Honors (Box 64)
    - Medallion - Rice University Service Award, 1967 (Box 64)
    - Plaque - National Science Foundation Science and Technology Center Pioneer Award, 1989-2000 (Box 64)
    - Plaque - The Sixth International Symposium on High Performance Distributed Computing, August 5-8, 1997 (Box 64)
    - Plaque - IPDPS Keynote Speaker, 2000 (Box 64)
    - Plaque - IPDPS Best Paper Award, 2001 (Box 64)
    - Plaque - IPDPS Keynote Speaker, 2004 (Box 64)
    - Plaque - Rice University, celebrating 35 years of service (Box 64)
    - Plaque - Rice University, celebrating 35 years of service (duplicate, with box) (Box 64)
    - Computing Research Association Distinguished Service Award, 1999 (Box 64)
    - Georgia Tech College of Computing appreciation of dedication and service, 2001-2003 (Box 64)
    - acm - unidentified (Box 64)
    - Unidentified award/paper weight (Box 64)
    - Plate - RCI 1999 Seymour Cray HPCC Industry Recognition Award (Box 64)
    - Commendation Poster from President Clinton (Box 65)
    - Banner from 2004 ComputerWorld Award Gala (Box 65)
    - NCSA National Technology Gird (Box 65)
    - Computer World Honors Laureate Certificate 2004 (Box 65)
    - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, Inc Certificate 1995 (Box 65)
    - Samuel C. Conte Distinguished Lecture Series Plaque 1997 (Box 65)
    - University of Wisconsin- La Crosse Plaque 2000 (Box 65)
- Series VIII: Audio-visual media, 1991-1997
  - CRPC VHS Tapes: An Introduction to the Next Generation Internet (Box 66, Item 1)
  - CRPC VHS Tapes: Portfolio Presentation 14 April 1995 (Box 66, Item 2)
  - CRPC VHS Tapes: Baylor College of Medicine's VNS Demo, CSW, MEDLINE (Box 66, Item 3)
  - CRPC VHS Tapes: Unlabeled (Box 66, Item 4)
  - CRPC VHS Tapes: CRPC Short Course 1-24-91 (tape 5 of 7) (Box 66, Item 5)
  - CRPC VHS Tapes: CRPC Short Course 1-24-91 (tape 6 of 7) (Box 66, Item 6)
  - CRPC VHS Tapes: CRPC Short Course 1-24-91 (tape 7 of 7) (Box 66, Item 7)
  - CRPC VHS Tapes: HOV, with Linda Torczon and Mary Wheeler, 11 April 1995 (Box 66, Item 8)
  - CRPC VHS Tapes: Baylor College of Medicine's Environmental Information Workstation (Box 66, Item 9)
  - CRPC VHS Tapes: Supercomputing SuperViz 1994 Washington D.C. (Box 66, Item 10)
  - CRPC VHS Tapes: Virtual Reality at the University of Illinois. May 1997 (Box 66, Item 11)
  - CRPC VHS Tapes: CRPC Short Course 1-24-91 (Tapes 1-4) (Box 66, Item 12)
  - CRPC CDs: CRPC 1996 GirlGames (Box 66, Item 13)
  - CRPC CDs: CRPC/GirlGames 1996 Prototype MAC (2 copies) (Box 66, Item 14)
  - CRPC CDs: CRPC GirlGames includes G2 (Box 66, Item 15)
- Series IX: Centers, addendum
  - Subseries A: GRADS and VGRADS (Box 66)
  - Subseries B: CPRC book files, 1999-2006
    - CPRC book, 1999-2000 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - CPRC book teleconference, Dec. 2000 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - CPRC book, early draft, Feb. 2000 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - CPRC book draft, 2001 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - CPRC book, Denise Penrose visit, Dec. 2001 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - CPRC book teleconference, Jan. 2002 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - CPRC book, contacts list and draft, Feb. 2002 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - CPRC book teleconference, May 2002 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - CPRC book, author bios, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - CPRC book, editor bios, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - CPRC book, contract documents, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - CPRC book, release to marketing form, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - CPRC book, author contact list, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - CPRC book teleconference, May 2002 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - CPRC book contacts list, 2001-2006 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- Series X: Ken Kennedy bios, memorials
  - Ken Kennedy bio, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence regarding Kennedy academic genealogy, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - JPDC in memorium (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Ken Audrey Kennedy Chair correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Rice / Copmputer Science online memorial for Ken Kennedy (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Kennedy' bio on Computer Science website (Box 67, Folder 21)
- Series XI: Laptop, 2007
  Scope and Contents
  Digital contents of laptop owned by Ken Kennedy. Materials were transferred to Woodson Research Center in 2007.
- Series XII: Digital content
  - Rice Office of Financial Aid charts, tables, reports, letters (Box 63)
  - Rice Office of Financial Aid student budget tables (Box 63)
  - Rice Financial Aid Task Force report (Box 63)
  - Welch Foundation letters and other scientific documents (Box 63)
  - Various charts: Salary, enrollment, donations, graduation numbers (Box 63)
  - Supercomputing conference documents (Box 63)
  - Duncan Hall floor plan images (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - CRPC/NSCA budgeting information, organizational correspondence (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Rice Engineering competitive assessment memo draft (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Rice Financial Aid Task Force National Merit Scholars letter (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Applied math solvers, table of expenses (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Various Rice payroll and expenses charts (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Malcolm Gillis/David H. Auston remarks, Renaissance Weekend/Lovett Brown Day 1995 (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - MSRC executive summary, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Malcolm Gillis/David Auston correspondence, assets and liabilities charts (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Faculty salary letters (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - David H. Auston annual research reports, Columbia University Department of Electrical Engineering (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Rice Graduate Education article, "faculty scores" (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Rice Strategic Planning Committee formation documents (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Rice faculty salary chart (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Fondren Library comparative expenditure reports (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Rice Policy 201-97: Faculty Appointments, Promotion, and Tenure guidelines (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Rice Policy 201-97: Faculty Appointments, Promotion, and Tenure guidelines + Linda Driskill letter to Promotion and Tenure Committees (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Rice faculty salary letters (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - David H. Auston Rice Engineering Dean letters (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - National Academy of Engineering annual meeting notes (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Two David H. Auston letters (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - David H. Auston letter re: Julia Mile Chance Prize (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - "The Living Library" PowerPoint presentation by Michael Keller (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Rice faculty enhancements, 1993-1997 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Centers and institutes at Rice (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Rice financial aid policy report (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Rice faculty enhancements, 1993-1999 (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - Jones School draft Steering Committee Report (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - Strategic Planning Committee "Rice: The Next Century" report drafts and comments (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - Rice financial aid/student expense table, 1976-1993 (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - Policy document drafts: Procedure for Investigating Accusations Warranting Severe Sanctions, Including Dismissal, Against Faculty Members; Draft Policy 201-97: Faculty Appointments, Promotions, and Tenure (Box 63, Folder 43)